hi welcome to this Oracle code session
嗨，欢迎参加本Oracle代码会议
today we will discuss resting in a
今天我们将讨论在
synchronous world so the goal of this
同步世界，所以这个目标
session is to discuss restful web
会议是讨论宁静的网络
services given that we are working with
鉴于我们与之合作的服务
Java we will base our discussion on a
Java，我们将基于
jaxa right now this session will
jaxa现在此会议将
basically look at 2 angle we will
基本上看2个角度
contrast and compare synchronous
对比和同步比较
approach and a synchronous approach now
现在的方法和同步方法
we will do that for both producing rest
我们将为双方提供休息
endpoints and consuming rest endpoint so
端点和消耗剩余端点
that basically means that we will look
这基本上意味着我们将
at what a sink and sink mean on the
一沉到底意味着什么
client side but also on the server side
客户端，也可以在服务器端
so let's first discuss the client side
让我们先讨论客户端
so in the Java space we have jax-rs
所以在Java空间中，我们有jax-rs
jax-rs stands for java api for restful
jax-rs代表Java api带来宁静
web services it's a standard base API
Web服务，这是一个标准的基本API
that we can use to produce rest endpoint
我们可以用来产生剩余端点
and since jax-rs - we can also use that
由于jax-rs-我们也可以使用
API to consume rest endpoint so if you
消耗剩余端点的API，因此如果您
look at jax-rs prior to a jack's rise to
在杰克升起之前先看看jax-rs
jax-rs was basically an easy to use
jax-rs基本上是一个易于使用的
frameworks that you would use to expose
您将用来公开的框架
rest endpoint it was part of Java EE
其余端点，它是Java EE的一部分
having said that you can also use Jack's
说了也可以用杰克的
right chakras outside of Java so you can
Java之外的右脉轮，因此您可以
use address just on top of Java C so
使用地址就在Java C之上
prior to tax rest - you had an easy to
休税前-您很容易
use server-side framework to expose
使用服务器端框架公开
endpoint but when it comes to consuming
终点，但涉及消费
those endpoints you basically had to
这些端点你基本上必须
write yourself the code to do that and
写自己的代码来做到这一点，
either you were you would use an API
无论您是使用API
such as the HTTP URL connection from the
例如来自
JDK which is a very old and very
JDK很老很老
low-level API so there was clearly
低级API，因此显然
mismatch between the client-side so that
客户端之间的不匹配
how we would consume the rest endpoint
我们将如何消耗其余端点
and the server side on the server side
而服务器端在服务器端
you had a very easy to use API
您有一个非常易于使用的API
API so you had to do that either using a
API，因此您必须使用
low-level API or you could rely on tough
低级API或您可以依靠强硬
patty solution this was solved in jax-rs
帕蒂解决方案，这是在JAX-RS解决
too with the addition of client-side API
也增加了客户端API
so now in jax-rs injector is - we have a
所以现在在jax-rs注射器中-我们有一个
server-side API that we can use to
我们可以使用的服务器端API
expose rest endpoint but we also have a
公开其余端点，但我们也有一个
client-side API that we can use to
我们可以使用的客户端API
consume is lead those rest endpoints so
消费领先于其他终点
today i will discuss about jax-rs -
今天我将讨论jax-rs-
which is the current version of the
这是当前版本
specification J's are 3 3 9 which is
规格J是3 3 9
part of Java e7 but again you can also
Java e7的一部分，但同样您也可以
use a phrase outside of Java EE so
在Java EE之外使用短语
purely on top of July C I will also
仅在7月，CI还将
discuss partly as access to 1 which is a
讨论作为对1的访问的一部分
next version of the specification which
规范的下一个版本
should be released during the summer
应该在夏天发布
this year and that is GSR three seven
今年，那就是GSR三七
zero which should be part of to evaluate
零，应作为评估的一部分
something which is important to mention
重要的事情要提
and I will based my discussion on jax-rs
我将基于jax-rs进行讨论
and I will use Jersey because it's the
我将使用Jersey，因为它是
open source reference implementation of
的开源参考实现
jax-rs but given the fact that sector ax
jax-rs，但考虑到扇区ax的事实
is a small ax typically I see you can
通常是小斧头，我看你可以
obviously use any compliant
显然使用任何合规的
implementation such as a refugee apache
难民阿帕奇等实施
wink and so on and so on
眨眼等等
so actually there is nothing really
所以实际上没有任何东西
specific to Jersey during this session
在本届会议期间特定于泽西岛
so let's look at all the jax-rs
让我们来看看所有的jax-rs
23 egg works
23个鸡蛋制品
we first need to have a client instance
我们首先需要一个客户实例
we get a jax-rs client instance through
我们通过获取一个jax-rs客户实例
this very simple bootstrap mechanism so
这个非常简单的引导机制
client builder new client will get us a
客户建设者新客户将为我们提供
client instance that we can use then
我们可以使用的客户端实例
from that Kent we will have to construct
从那个肯特，我们将不得不构建
a web resource target a web resource
Web资源目标Web资源
target it just is just the location of
目标只是它的位置
the network where our remote endpoint is
我们的远程端点所在的网络
then based on the target we will
然后根据目标，我们将
actually construct the request itself so
实际上构造请求本身
in this case let's say that we want to
在这种情况下，假设我们要
get the forecast of the city of Paris so
得到巴黎市的预报
that's why we are setting some query
这就是为什么我们要设置一些查询
parameters we also use the get HTTP
参数我们也使用get HTTP
verbs given that we want to get a
给定我们想要得到的动词
resource from the network and we also
来自网络的资源，我们也
specify what response type we expect to
指定我们期望的响应类型
get from the remote endpoint in this
从远程端点获取
case this is a focus class and you see
案例，这是一个焦点课程，你会看到
that the result of our invocation is
我们调用的结果是
indeed of type forecast now given the
鉴于
fact that we have this kind container
事实上，我们有这种容器
and this kind container is a relatively
这种容器相对来说
edgy object we need to make sure that we
锋利的对象，我们需要确保我们
close that time container once we are
一旦我们关闭了时间容器
done so injector is - we have this new
这样做是注射器-我们有这个新的
client API it's a fluent API so that
客户端API，它是流利的API，因此
means that it's a very easy to use API
表示这是一个非常易于使用的API
where you will basically chain all the
基本上，您将在其中链接所有
method invocation to construct your
方法调用以构造您的
request
请求
so it's like a phrase where you actually
所以就像一个短语
step-by-step you specify what you want
逐步指定您要的内容
to do what you want to get from your
做你想从你那里得到的
waste invocation so and the API itself
因此浪费了调用，API本身
introduced different new objects like
引入了不同的新对象，例如
the trial container that we have already
我们已经拥有的试用容器
mentioned it's so if you don't decieve
提到是这样，如果你不欺骗
anything if pacific convention over
如果太平洋公约结束
configuration what if you see you have
配置，如果您看到有
the ability to customize that client
定制该客户的能力
container we then have a web target so a
容器，然后我们有一个网络目标
web resource target which is likely some
网络资源目标，可能是一些
kind of glorify your i it's
荣耀你我是
the location on the network of our
我们网络上的位置
remote endpoint to construct a web
远程端点构建网站
target from a client container and the
客户端容器中的目标和
nice thing about the jax-rs client API
关于jax-rs客户端API的好处
is that it basically shares a lot of the
基本上是分享了很多
concept that we have on the server side
我们在服务器端拥有的概念
so we have the notion of path obviously
所以我们显然有路径的概念
we also have support for templates like
我们也支持模板
we have on server side we have support
我们在服务器端有支持
for query parameters matrix parameters
用于查询参数矩阵参数
and so on and so on so if you are
依此类推，依此类推，如果您是
already familiar with ajax is service
已经熟悉ajax的服务
ipi you will see that the client-side
ipi，您将看到客户端
API is very simple to learn and we also
API非常简单易学，我们也
have this notion of request invocation
具有这种请求调用的概念
builder where basically you have really
基本上您真正拥有的建筑商
the ability to customize your request
定制您的要求的能力
like you have the ability to set the
就像你有能力设置
cookies what media type you expect to
Cookies您希望使用哪种媒体类型
get set the headers and so on and so on
设置标题等等
obviously your security to define web
显然，定义网络的安全性
which HTTP verbs you want to use
您想使用哪些HTTP动词
something to mention is the exact rest
值得一提的是确切的休息
one's also having the ability to set the
一个人也有能力设定
visited or services we will come to that
访问或服务，我们将来到
later on
稍后的
the flow of the invocation as we have
调用流程
already seen is very simple so we have a
已经看过非常简单，所以我们有一个
client container from that land
来自那个土地的客户集装箱
container we will construct a web target
容器，我们将构建一个网络目标
and from that web target we will
从该网络目标中，我们将
construct our request and book that
构建我们的请求并预订
request to get a response if we look at
要求得到回应，如果我们看
that example it is the liquid some
那个例子是液体
example the only thing is that this time
唯一的例子是这次
we are specifying that we expect to get
我们指定我们希望得到
some JSON type in return we also set
作为回报，我们还设置了一些JSON类型
some headers and in this case we don't
一些标题，在这种情况下，我们不
want to have one single forecast but we
想要一个单一的预测，但是我们
want to have a little forecast so that's
希望有一点预测，所以
why we are using this generic type of
为什么我们使用这种通用类型的
Vista of forecast now the tracker is
现在预测的Vista跟踪器是
client API has also the notion of
客户端API也具有以下概念
invoker so if you look at this example
调用者，所以如果您看这个例子
this is the example that we have been
这是我们一直在做的例子
using until now we haven't specified an
直到现在我们还没有指定
invoker so that means that we are
调用者，这意味着我们
getting the default behavior and by
获取默认行为并通过
default the invoker that we have
默认我们拥有的调用者
originating is a synchronous invoker so
发起是同步调用者，因此
that means that this is a blocking call
这意味着这是一个阻止呼叫
so that means that as soon as the count
所以这意味着一旦计数
sorry the get method is invoked on the
抱歉，get方法在上被调用
client that method will block until the
客户端将一直阻塞该方法，直到
response has been sent by the remote
响应已由远程发送
endpoint so this is really a blocking
端点，所以这确实是一个障碍
call the good news is that is that
打电话来的好消息是
jax-ur is - is also an asynchronous
jax-ur是-也是异步的
invoker - introduced invoker basically
invoker-基本介绍的调用者
allows us to consume rest endpoint in a
允许我们在
non-blocking fashion to do that it's
无阻碍的时尚做到这一点
exactly the same api the only thing that
完全一样的api唯一的优点是
we have to specify is that we need to
我们必须指定的是，我们需要
specify that we want to use the async
指定我们要使用异步
invoker and you see at the bottom of
调用者，您会在底部看到
this slide I'm invoking this icing
这张幻灯片，我正在为此锦上添花
method so this is basically to tell that
方法，这基本上是为了告诉
to the objectors can container that I
反对者可以把我的容器
want to use an icing invoker and the
想要使用结冰调用程序，并且
difference here is that as soon as we do
区别在于，只要我们这样做
we do the get invocation the method we
我们执行get调用的方法
will return directly and if you look at
将直接返回，如果您查看
the return type that we get from these
从这些中得到的返回类型
Oracle's invocation this is not a string
Oracle的调用这不是字符串
or but it's a future type of type string
或者，但这是字符串类型的未来类型
so that means that we have a future
这意味着我们有未来
object that we'll be able to use at some
我们可以在某些地方使用的对象
point to actually get the result of our
指向实际得到我们的结果
I think rest invocation so to do a
我想休息一下，所以要做一个
remote and point a synchronous
远程并指向一个同步
invocation we basically need to tell on
我们基本上需要讲的调用
the client side that so we balakey need
因此，我们的客户端需要
to tell to our objective client
告诉我们的目标客户
container that we want to be dancing
我们想跳舞的容器
invoker to do that we just need to use
调用者可以做到这一点，我们只需要使用
the ethic method while we conserve the
道德方法，同时我们保留
request so you see that in this case
请求，这样您就可以看到
what we get in return
我们得到的回报
is our future off string so that means
是我们未来的束缚，这意味着
that we have a future object that we can
我们有一个未来的目标，我们可以
query later on to actually get the
稍后查询以实际获取
result of our with the remote endpoint
我们与远程端点的结果
location the problem is that if it takes
位置的问题是，如果需要
a long time for the server to send the
服务器发送了很长时间
response our call to the get metal not
回应我们对get metal的呼吁
know future object will be basically
知道未来的对象将基本上
blocking waiting for that result and
阻止等待该结果，并
worse than that if for some reason the
比这更糟糕的是，由于某种原因
server if the remote endpoint is not
服务器，如果远程端点不是
able to send the result our client
能够将结果发送给我们的客户
application will wait forever for that
应用程序将永远等待
result that will never come so we need
结果永远不会到来，所以我们需要
to make sure that we set a timeout so
确保我们设置了超时时间
this is some example but you see that
这是一些例子，但是你看到
this time we set a timeout of five
这次我们设置了五个超时
seconds while we do a get invocation on
进行调用的秒数
the future object so that means that
未来的对象，这意味着
this future object would be query for
这个未来的对象将被查询
maximum five seconds after that time
在此之后最多五秒钟
exception will be raised so our
将会引发异常，因此我们
application will not block even if the
即使
server is not able to sender the
服务器无法发送
response but there's still an issue if
回应，但如果仍然存在问题
so that means that our application might
因此，这意味着我们的应用程序可能
in worst case scenario be blocked for
在最坏的情况下被阻止
five seconds so that means that
五秒钟，这意味着
basically our client side thread will be
基本上我们的客户端线程将是
blocked for puffs at five seconds this
五秒钟阻塞吹气
is athis is a big issue because that
这是一个大问题，因为
thread is directly not able to do
线程直接无法执行
anything else
还要别的吗
so if we are using the same that
所以如果我们使用相同的
particular thread for example to update
特定线程，例如更新
the UI our UI will be frozen for five
用户界面我们的用户界面将冻结五个
seconds
秒
given that it's a future object we can
鉴于这是一个未来的目标，我们可以
do something like that instead of
做这样的事情而不是
invoking the get on the feature object
调用要素对象上的get
which is in itself a blocking call we
这本身就是一个封锁电话
can check the is done and Ethan is
可以检查是否已完成，而Ethan是
basically through once we have the
基本上，一旦我们有了
result
结果
so once the feature is completed or has
所以一旦功能完成或具有
been cancelled or an exception has been
被取消或发生了异常
raised
提高
that is a workaround to overcome that
这是克服该问题的解决方法
issue but still it's not very practical
问题，但仍然不是很实用
once we have we are sure that is done is
一旦我们拥有，我们确定完成的是
true we can actually invoke the get
是的，我们实际上可以调用get
method on the future object which in
关于未来对象的方法
this case we know I will not be blocking
这种情况下，我们知道我不会阻止
it in this case it's also a good idea to
在这种情况下，这也是一个好主意
set the client container timer because
设置客户端容器计时器，因为
we want to make sure that the get
我们要确保得到
request so the the get rest invocation
请求，以便获取休息调用
doesn't text too long something which is
不会太久发短信是
also part of jax-rs too
也是jax-rs的一部分
on the client side is what what we call
在客户端这就是我们所说的
an a synchronous invocation callback
同步调用回调
that we can use it's basically a very
我们可以使用它基本上是一个非常
simple interface who has two method 1
简单界面谁有两种方法1
method is completed so that method is a
方法完成，所以方法是
basically a callback that will be
基本上是一个回调
invoked when the a synchronous response
同步响应时调用
has been processed and the second
已经处理，第二个
callback is a fel method that method is
回调是一个妖怪的方法
automatically invoked a Finneran
自动调用Finneran
exception has been thrown so if there
引发了异常，所以如果存在
has been an issue in the invocation so
在调用中一直是一个问题，所以
it works like this as usual construct
它像往常一样构造
from the client the resource target we
来自客户的资源目标
are using the I think invoker given that
鉴于我正在使用我认为的调用者
it's an asynchronous invocation that we
这是我们的异步调用
want to do we are using the get HTTP
想做的我们正在使用get HTTP
verbs method but this time we pass an
动词方法，但是这次我们通过了
instance of an invocation callback and
调用回调的实例，以及
remember that invocation callback as to
记住关于
call back the first one completed so
叫回第一个完成的
that's the invocation callback that is
那是调用回调
invoked once we have the result from the
一旦我们获得了
remote endpoint
远程端点
the second callback is the cell method
第二个回调是cell方法
that would be invoked if something goes
如果有事情会被调用
wrong now if you look at the definition
如果您看一下定义，现在错了
of the invocation callback we have
我们拥有的调用回调
defining parametrize type in this case
在这种情况下定义参数化类型
this is a customer so that means that
这是一个客户，所以这意味着
what we expect to get from the remote
我们期望从远程获得什么
endpoint is a customer type you see that
端点是一种客户类型，您会看到
the return of that resource invocation
该资源调用的返回
is a future object of type customer and
是类型为customer的未来对象，并且
you also see that the completed callback
您还看到完成的回调
is expecting to get a customer type as
期望获得客户类型为
parameter make sense that's what we
参数有意义，这就是我们
expect to get back from the invocation
希望从调用中得到回报
now let's move on and let's put that
现在让我们继续前进，让我们
into this perspective here we have a
从这个角度来看，我们有一个
simple micro-services typical scenario
简单的微服务典型场景
where we have one travel agency services
我们有一个旅行社服务
that will be the kind of multiple back
那将是多种背
end
结束
read services the scenario is as follow
阅读服务场景如下
so we have a user coming in through the
所以我们有一个用户通过
travel agency services and that travel
旅行社服务和那次旅行
agency services would like to propose to
代理服务想建议
that user some potential destination
该用户的潜在目的地
that you might want to visit so the user
您可能要访问的用户
gets to the travel agency services the
到旅行社服务
first services that will be invoked will
将要调用的第一个服务将
be the customer services so the idea is
是客户服务，所以这个主意是
that we first need to have some kind of
首先我们需要某种
history for that given customer based on
该给定客户的历史记录基于
that the travel agency services will
旅行社服务将
invoke the destinations received the
调用接收到的目的地
idea of that services is to provide some
该服务的想法是提供一些
potential destination for that user so
该用户的潜在目的地，因此
that means that the travel agency has
这意味着旅行社有
now a list of potential potential
现在列出潜在的
destination to suggest and what we also
建议的目的地，我们还
want to do is that for each destination
要做的是针对每个目的地
that we are about to suggest we want to
我们将建议我们要
invoke the weather services and the
调用气象服务和
quoting services to add some weather
报价服务以增加一些天气
information to each destination but also
信息到每个目的地，而且
we also want to have some price
我们也想要一些价格
information to the destination that we
信息到目的地，我们
are about to suggest to the user once we
即将向用户建议
have all those results we basically
具有所有这些结果，我们基本上
combine them and send them back to the
合并它们并将它们发送回
user so the user we
用户，所以我们
get a list of potential destination that
得到一个潜在目的地的清单
you might want to visit with for each
您可能想与每个人一起访问
destination according to a price
根据价格的目的地
information and some weather forecasts
信息和一些天气预报
now obviously given that we have
现在显然，鉴于我们有
multiple services to consume we
多种服务消耗我们
basically need to implement some
基本上需要实施一些
workflow so the travel agency services
工作流程，因此旅行社服务
will have some kind of very basic
会有一些非常基本的
equation layer to invoke the different
等式层调用不同
services so the first service is to
服务，所以第一项服务是
invoke the customer services based on
调用基于
that it will invoke the destination
它将调用目标
services and once it has all the
服务，一旦拥有了所有
destination it will invoke in parallel
它将并行调用的目标
the weather service services and the
气象服务和
coating services so it's very obvious
涂层服务，因此非常明显
that a pure synchronous approach doesn't
纯粹的同步方法不会
really make sense for such an approach
这种方法真的很有意义
this is a very simple scenario but still
这是一个非常简单的场景，但仍然
in terms of performance it would be very
在性能方面，这将是非常
bad basically the the time it takes to
基本上是很糟糕的时间
get the result to the end-user would
将结果提供给最终用户
basically be the addition of all the
基本上是所有
individual requests that the travels and
个人要求旅行和
the services as to do so this is not
这样做的服务不是
something that we want to do it's clear
我们想要做的事情很明显
that we have to go a synchronous for
我们必须同步
that and let's simplify that services
并简化服务
and only look at two services we just
只看两个服务
want to simplify the workflow and invoke
想简化工作流程并调用
the destination services so we want to
目的地服务，所以我们想
have some destination and for each
有一些目的地，每个目的地
destination we want to have some weather
我们想要一些天气的目的地
information we want to do that in an
我们想要在
asynchronous fashion so if we look at
异步方式，所以如果我们看一下
the code this would looks like this we
看起来像这样的代码
first do a request to the destination
首先向目的地提出要求
services to get some recommended or some
服务获得一些推荐或一些
suggestion obviously we are using the
建议显然我们正在使用
sync invoker we have to specify an
同步调用程序，我们必须指定一个
education callback remember an
教育回调记得
invocation callback you need to have to
您需要执行的调用回调
call back the first one is a completed
回电话第一个是完成的
callback that will be invoked once we
一旦我们调用回调
have all the result from the invocation
具有调用的所有结果
in this case we would get a list of this
在这种情况下，我们将获得此列表
nation so a list of potential suggestion
国家，因此有潜在建议的清单
that we might want to provide to the
我们可能想提供给
user then we would basically go over
用户，那么我们基本上会过去
that list and for all the element of
该列表以及所有元素
that list we would do another rest
那个清单，我们会再休息
request again we have to do that in a
再次请求，我们必须在
sequence fashion so we use do a sync
序列时尚，所以我们使用做同步
invoker given that it's nothing
调用者认为这没什么
invocation we have to specify an
调用我们必须指定一个
invocation call back when invocation
调用时调用
call back needs to have to call back
回电需要回电
define so the first one is the one that
定义，所以第一个是那个
will invoked whenever we have all the
只要我们拥有所有
results now we also have to make sure
结果，我们还必须确保
that we provide the thread callback for
我们提供的线程回调
the - I think request that we are doing
-我认为我们正在做的要求
so we would have something like that
所以我们会有这样的事情
so I get that you see that that kind of
所以我知道你看到那种
code is getting a little bit difficult
代码变得有点困难
to write and that means that at the end
写，这意味着最后
of the day we would have a called that
那天我们会打电话给
is all difficult to write debug and
很难编写调试信息，
maintain you also see that the error
维护您还看到错误
handling is basically a spread across
处理基本上遍布
our code so it's clearly something which
我们的代码，所以很明显
is a bit difficult and why is that well
有点困难，为什么会这样
we said that we want to go synchronous
我们说过要同步
because we want to get the the
因为我们想要得到
performance and the scalability we don't
性能和可扩展性，我们没有
want to be blocking to do that we have
想要阻止我们这样做
to use the ransom from the API but given
使用来自API的赎金
that they are dependency between our
他们是我们之间的依赖
services we see that this API doesn't
服务，我们看到这个API并没有
really fit that model where we have to
确实适合我们需要的模型
invoke in an asset instruction multiple
在一个资产指令中调用多个
services and each services as dependency
服务和每个服务的依赖关系
between another services so it doesn't
在其他服务之间，所以它不会
really work Zachary's - as to invoker
扎卡里（Zachary）的确很有效-对于调用者
the default invoker which is a
默认调用者是
synchronous invoker so that means that
同步调用者，这意味着
it's blocking and it has also another
它正在阻塞，并且还有另一个
introducing proper this is the I think
介绍适当的这是我认为
method injectors - one is adding a
方法注入器-一个正在添加一个
thousand blocker it's a reactive a
万千阻滞剂是反应性的
synchronous invoker it's the RX method
同步调用程序是RX方法
that you see at the bottom of the slide
您在幻灯片底部看到的
and you see that one when we are using
当我们使用时，您会看到一个
that invoker what we get in return for
该调用者我们得到的回报
the
的
requesting location is of type
请求位置是类型
compression stage so let's quickly talk
压缩阶段，让我们快速谈谈
about the completion stage API it's a
关于完成阶段的API
new API that was added to delay see 8
已添加以延迟的新API参见8
and I'll deny thing about that API is
我会否认有关该API的事情是
that we had the notion of a state of
我们有一个状态的概念
stage being an operation computation
阶段是一个运算
that performs an action or computer
执行动作或计算机
value in a synchronous fashion and we
以同步的方式实现价值，我们
have the ability to basically chain
有能力基本连锁
different stage so we can define a flow
不同的阶段，所以我们可以定义一个流程
of different stage that needs to be
不同阶段的需要
invoked in a specific order
按特定顺序调用
so on termination of a stage a stage may
因此，在阶段结束时，一个阶段可能会
in turn trigger another dependent stage
进而触发另一个依赖阶段
execution now if you look at the
现在看一下执行
compression stage RDoc it the API itself
压缩阶段RDoc it API本身
might seem a little bit daunting it has
似乎有些令人生畏
a lot of methods it has around 40
它有大约40种方法
methods to grasp the API you just have
掌握API的方法
to understand a few concept and for each
了解一些概念，每个概念
concept there is logical keywords and
概念有逻辑关键字和
that keywords will basically be used to
该关键字将基本上用于
construct the method that you're going
构造您要使用的方法
to use so that's why we are lot of
使用，这就是为什么我们很多
methods but at the end of the day those
方法，但归根结底
methods are just basically a combination
方法基本上只是一种组合
of different behavior for example on one
不同的行为，例如一个
stage execution we may trigger another
阶段执行，我们可能会触发另一个
stage so if you just want to trigger the
因此，如果您只想触发
execution of another stage you will use
执行另一个阶段，您将使用
it then keyword but if you want to
然后关键字，但如果你想
trigger the execution of a given stage
触发给定阶段的执行
once to a given stage are completed you
一旦完成给定阶段，您
would use a combined stage and if you
将使用组合阶段，如果
want to trigger the education of first
想触发初等教育
stage on if one one of the two
如果两者之一
completion stage are done you will use
完成阶段，您将使用
the other keywords so other concept that
其他关键字等等
you have to know does the computation
你必须知道计算
takes an argument and returns a result
接受参数并返回结果
for example we have the hot light
例如我们有热灯
keywords so that means that you are
关键字，这意味着您
going to supply the function with a
将为功能提供一个
result of the previous stage as argument
前一阶段的结果作为参数
and that function will return the result
该函数将返回结果
you have to accept keyword that one
你必须接受一个
takes a consumer I need only technology
需要一个消费者，我只需要技术
so it doesn't return anything given that
因此它不会返回任何内容
it's a consumer you also have the run
是消费者，您也有机会
keywords that takes a runnable so it
具有可运行性的关键字
doesn't have an argument and Inter's and
没有论点，国米的和
returning results another concept with
返回结果的另一个概念
its keywords that you would have to
您必须使用的关键字
understand is a out execution of the
理解是对
compression the do computation is
压缩做计算是
arranged so if the letter doesn't hand
这样安排，如果字母不交
with the I think keywords that means
我认为关键字意味着
that we are using the stage the default
我们正在使用舞台默认
execution facilities but only high on
执行设施，但只有高
the other hand if the method ends with a
另一方面，如果该方法以a结尾
sink that means that we want to use the
下沉意味着我们要使用
stage default a synchronous execution
阶段默认同步执行
facilities and in addition you also have
设施，此外您还拥有
the ability to pass specific a trivet or
通过特定的trivet或
services so basically to view the
服务基本上就是看
compression stage API you will have to
压缩阶段的API
combine those different keywords to
结合这些不同的关键字来
basically obtain the method that you
基本上获得您所使用的方法
want to use so for example you have to
想要使用，例如，您必须
then accept method then you if you want
然后接受方法，然后如果你想要
to perform that in a synchronous action
以同步动作执行
you have to done except I think or then
除了我认为，然后
except with the ability to pass an
除了能够通过
executor and so on or you might have
遗嘱执行人等等，否则您可能会有
done except both if you want to wait for
完成，除了两个，如果你想等待
the execution of both completion stage
两个完成阶段的执行
before triggering another completion
在触发另一个完成之前
stage or then accept both passing method
阶段或然后接受两种通过方法
and so on and so on so to get the
依此类推，等等
constants a GPA you really need to
常数您真正需要的GPA
understand those different keywords and
了解那些不同的关键字，
then it's just a matter of using the
那只是使用
right method if we look at an example we
正确的方法，如果我们看一个例子，我们
have a first request so this one's
有第一个要求，所以这个
requested to remote endpoint with some
请求与一些远程端点
pricing information for a given
给定价格信息
destination you see that we are using we
目的地，您看到我们正在使用我们
are using the Oracle invoker and then we
正在使用Oracle调用程序，然后我们
have a second request this one is used
还有第二个要求
to get the forecast information for a
得到一个的预测信息
given destination and again you see that
给定目的地，您再次看到
we are using to our it invoker so it
我们正在使用它的it调用程序，所以它
that means that what we get in return is
这意味着我们得到的回报是
to completion stage
到完成阶段
when both states complete normally the
当两种状态都正常完成时
two result are passed to the function
两个结果传递给函数
that we have here so that's what that's
我们在这里，那就是
why we're using two then combined so
为什么我们使用两个然后合并
that if we are for the first compression
如果我们是第一次压缩
stage and we want to exhibit that one
舞台，我们想展示一个
and the second compression stage so the
第二个压缩阶段
GS F once we have the result they are
GS F一旦我们得到了结果
passed to the function which in this
传递给其中的功能
case is reserved if affordable method
如果负担得起的方法保留案例
that get that get as a parameter of the
得到的得到作为的参数
to result of the invocation so the
导致调用的结果
following example obtains in parallel so
以下示例并行获取
in another construction of price and a
在另一种价格和结构中
forecast for the destination and it
预测目的地及其
makes a reservation if some specific
如果有一些特定的保留
condition rmx so this is basically a new
条件rmx，所以这基本上是一个新的
injector as to one we have this new
关于一个喷油器，我们有这个新的
Ericsson rocker that allows you to
爱立信摇杆，让您
consume in a synchronous fashion remote
以同步方式消费
rest endpoint and then I think about
休息终点，然后我思考
that API is that we are using the Java
该API是我们正在使用Java
jet compressing Search API to basically
喷射压缩搜索API基本上
define the dependency between the
定义之间的依赖关系
services that we want to invoked the
我们要调用的服务
completion stage is supported out of the
完成阶段受支持
box injectors to all those actors
所有这些演员的盒装注射器
implementation all the jacks or s21
实现所有插孔或s21
implementation must abort the
实现必须中止
compression stage API having said that
压缩阶段API表示
the goal of the specification is to make
规范的目标是使
it extensible and open to the octave
它可以扩展并打开八度
frameworks for example the Jersey plans
框架，例如泽西岛计划
to add support for rx Java let's look at
添加对rx Java的支持，让我们看一下
a quick demo to illustrate this so what
快速演示来说明这一点
I am running on my machine is the
我在我的机器上运行的是
basically this travel intensive services
基本上，这种旅行密集型服务
it's one of the vectors a sample that
它是向量的一个样本
sample has basically all this the
样本基本上具有所有这些
services needed to fulfill that scenario
实现该方案所需的服务
so we have travel urgency services and
所以我们有旅行紧急服务
then running on the same machine we have
然后在我们拥有的同一台机器上运行
the mythical back-end services the
神话般的后端服务
weather services destination services
天气服务目的地服务
and so on this is the gate of
等等，这是
that sample so basically we have
该样品，所以基本上我们有
identity services so this is basically
身份服务，所以这基本上是
the travel identity services and it has
旅行身份服务，它具有
multiple implementation it has a
多种实现，它有一个
synchronous implementation so if the
同步执行，因此如果
travel agency services will consume all
旅行社服务将消耗掉所有
the backend services using the
后端服务使用
traditional synchronous approach so the
传统的同步方法
booking one there is also a synchronous
预订一个也有一个同步
approach and finally we will also use
方法，最后我们还将使用
the completion stage again so the one
完成阶段再次如此
using the computers instead GPIO if we
如果我们使用计算机而不是GPIO
look here we also have remote services
看这里我们也有远程服务
so this remote services are basically
所以这个远程服务基本上是
the back-end services for example we
后端服务，例如我们
have is one remote destination visited
有一个访问过的偏远目的地
will give us a list of visited services
将给我们一份拜访服务的清单
so if we go to the URL so I'm going to
因此，如果我们转到URL，那么我将
my local machine where or 9090 let's see
我的本地机器在哪里或9090让我们看看
our extremal destination visited I
我们的极端目的地来了我
should have just talked this is what I
应该刚才说的这就是我的意思
get sold as summary story so this is
被作为摘要故事出售，所以这是
just a result of one services on your
只是您一项服务的结果
hanif am asking for recommended the
hanif要求推荐
deposit area where the user has to what
用户必须存放什么的存放区域
this nation was just to the user we have
这个国家只是给我们的用户
some result and so for example I can
一些结果，例如，我可以
also ask to ask some specific forecast
也要问一些具体的预测
for one given destination so we need to
对于一个给定的目的地，所以我们需要
give a city here this is just the result
给这里一个城市，这只是结果
of one location let's now invoke the
现在，我们来调用一个位置的
traditional travel
传统旅行
agenda to reseed using the pure
议事日程使用纯
synchronous synchronous
同步同步
approach so I'm using the synchronous
方法，所以我正在使用同步
agent and we see that well it takes a
代理，我们很好地看到了
bit of time ok now we have the result so
好的时间，现在我们有了结果，所以
that is a result that is composed of two
这是由两个组成的结果
are using location from the multiple
正在使用多个位置
services so we have all the history and
服务，因此我们拥有所有的历史和
we have a set of recommendation and you
我们有一套建议，您
see that for each recommendation we have
看到每个建议，我们都有
not only
不仅仅
destination but we'll serve some
目的地，但我们会为您服务
watering for some forecast information
浇灌一些预报信息
and some pricing information and we have
还有一些价格信息，我们有
that for five times what is interesting
五倍有趣的是
is at the end works out the total
最后算出总数
processing time and we see that for the
处理时间，我们看到
bottling approach to invoke all those
装瓶方法来调用所有这些
services basically necessary and fashion
服务基本必要和时尚
it takes more than four second same
同样要花四秒钟以上
approach but using now this time the
方法，但这次使用
asynchronous API object arise - and we
异步API对象的出现-我们
can have all the result we see that it
可以得到所有结果，我们看到了
was quite faster so we have all the
速度很快，所以我们拥有
destination that were visited and we
参观过的目的地，我们
have a set of suggestion with each time
每次都有一套建议
forecast and pricing information and the
预测和定价信息以及
processing time is all under one second
处理时间不到一秒钟
so it's really faster and last but not
所以它真的更快，最后但不是
least let's use the compression to the
至少让我们对
API and again it was very fast
API，再次非常快
so we are gonna have all the results on
所以我们将获得所有结果
this destination and the process state
此目的地和过程状态
processing time using the compression
使用压缩处理时间
stage is basically more is the same as
阶段基本上更多是相同的
distinct as the a synchronous approach
作为同步方法而与众不同
the takeaway here is that in terms of
这里的要点是
performance and scalability you should
您应该具有的性能和可伸缩性
go a synchronous approach and then you
采取同步方法，然后你
have a 2 choice header using the console
使用控制台有一个2选择标头
as a synchronous API or using the
作为同步API或使用
reactive as and release API and in terms
反应式和发布API以及术语
of performance you will basically get
基本上可以得到的性能
more than the same performance but
超过相同的性能，但
clearly if you have dependency between
显然，如果您之间有依赖性
your services and that's what we have
您的服务，这就是我们所拥有的
here so for example
例如这里
it doesn't make sense to invoke the
调用
Weather Service's before having the list
列出清单之前的气象服务
of suggested destination so if you have
建议的目的地，如果您有
dependency between your services then
然后您的服务之间的依赖
your code will be a lot easier to work
您的代码将更容易使用
using the reactive a synchronous API
使用反应式同步API
so in summary and we have injector s2 we
总而言之，我们有喷油器s2
have a client API that we can use to
有一个客户端API，我们可以用来
easily consume rest remote endpoint we
轻松消耗剩余的远程端点
have this client side container that
有这个客户端容器
basically hides a lot of the complexity
基本上隐藏了很多复杂性
for us so it's a high level API that we
对我们来说，这是我们的高级API
can use it has multiple invoker it has a
可以使用它有多个调用程序，它有一个
synchronous behavior that's one you are
同步行为就是你
not specifying an invoker you will get
没有指定您将得到的调用者
the default invoker which is blocking we
默认的调用者阻止了我们
have also net synchronous invoker that's
也有净同步调用者
part of Jack's rs-24 that you have to
杰克的rs-24的一部分，你必须
use the async invoker you see that in
使用异步调用程序，您会在
some case get my block so it even though
在某些情况下，即使遇到障碍
it's I think it my block because
我认为这是我的障碍，因为
remember that future I get might just
记住，我得到的未来可能只是
block waiting for the enter so if we
阻止等待输入，所以如果我们
want to get around that we can use the
想要绕过我们可以使用
invocation callback facilities that is
调用回调设施是
part of Jack's rise to the zero but we
杰克升为零的一部分，但我们
saw a so limitation typically when we
通常当我们看到这样的局限性
had multiple services to invoke and when
有多个服务要调用以及何时
we are
我们是
we had dependency between the services
我们在服务之间有依赖性
so it was not really easy to write such
所以写这样的书并不容易
a code so that is something that is
一个代码，所以这是
being solved in the access to one we did
在获得我们所做的解决方案中得到解决
new reactive invoker that the rx method
新的反应式调用者，即rx方法
that we are using to get reactive
我们用来反应的
invoker let's discuss the low side
调用者让我们讨论低端
breast to expose rest resources endpoint
乳房暴露休息资源终点
using the X rays we would have to do
使用X射线，我们将不得不做
something like list we have a class with
像清单，我们有一堂课
a few metals we are using the add Pat
我们正在使用添加Pat的一些金属
annotation to specific are the trusted
特定注释是受信任的
also specify that this is the you write
还指定这是你写的
for all those resources from that method
对于该方法的所有资源
and then we also use the same at
然后我们在
presentation on a given method specify
给出给定方法的说明
the sub path
子路径
example I'm also using a path parameter
示例我也在使用路径参数
that would be resulted from times and
那是由于时间和
finally I'm using that reduce in
最终我在使用减少
addition specify that this particular
另外指定此特定
rest resource end point is producing
剩余资源终点正在产生
that specific media type XML note that I
该特定媒体类型XML注释
haven't specified any HTTP verb so that
没有指定任何HTTP动词，因此
mean that I'm using the default one
表示我正在使用默认的
which is get and if you see I have the
这是得到的，如果你看到我有
ability to use different verbs like post
使用诸如post之类的不同动词的能力
in this example so in this case my rest
在这个例子中，在这种情况下，我的休息
endpoint is producing XML and it
端点正在生成XML，并且它
consumed XML also note that I'm using
使用的XML还请注意，我正在使用
some query parameter in this particular
一些特定的查询参数
example so this is termed objects our
例子，所以这被称为对象
scope that we have been using Tinder's
我们一直在使用Tinder的范围
now injects rise to we also have yogi to
现在注入上升，我们也有瑜伽士
the synchronous capability on the
上的同步能力
service value so it works like this so
服务价值，所以它像这样工作
we have a Jack's arrest which force
我们逮捕了杰克
method and note that we are injecting
方法并注意，我们正在注入
using the Ab suspended animation this
使用Ab暂停动画
new object
新对象
nothing response also note that this
没有反应也注意到
method is return void so it doesn't
方法是返回无效的，所以它不会
return anything so we now have these
返回任何东西，所以我们现在有了这些
sexers response that we can basically
Sexers回应，我们基本上可以
use to basically do the request
用于基本执行请求
processing in a different thread
在不同的线程中处理
so what I'm doing here let's say that
所以我在这里说的是
I'm in the Java environment so I'm using
我在Java环境中，因此我正在使用
a magnetic texture services to start a
磁性纹理服务开始
new thread in that thread I would do
我会在该线程中创建新线程
something that would I likely be very
我可能会非常
expensive in that sort of resources so I
这种资源很昂贵，所以我
have an external thread I'm running some
有一个外部线程，我正在运行一些
very long-running computation and then
非常长时间运行的计算，然后
have this a sink response subject that I
有一个我的沉沦反应主题
can use in my external thread to
可以在我的外部线程中使用
basically resumed the thread that was
基本上恢复了原来的线程
processing the incoming requests all of
处理所有传入请求
that is done using this analyzing
使用此分析完成
response object this approach gives out
该方法给出的响应对象
the ability to execute the business
执行业务的能力
logic in a different thread something
逻辑在不同的线程中
important to mention is that the
值得一提的是
underlying i/o thread is still blocking
底层I / O线程仍在阻塞
so that means that my client is still
所以这意味着我的客户仍然
blocked until my I think response is
直到我认为回应被封锁
video this is true on both sides of the
视频这在两边都是对的
connection connection so on the server
连接服务器上的连接
side and on the client side we have the
方面，在客户端，我们有
new Vasek response which now provide
现在提供新的Vasek响应
them in for a synchronous server-side or
它们用于同步服务器端或
respond processing so we have the
响应处理，所以我们有
ability to do the processing of the
处理能力
response in a different thread that we
在不同的线程中响应
create it's injected using this new
创建使用这个新的注入
extended annotation and we have
扩展注释，我们有
different way of working on that I think
我认为有不同的工作方式
response object so typically we inject
响应对象，因此通常我们注入
the right sync respond so we basically
正确的同步响应，所以我们基本上
suspend the thread we do the processing
暂停我们要处理的线程
in a different thread and in that
在不同的线程中
different thread at some point once we
一旦某个时候，我们在不同的线程
have the result we would resume the
有结果，我们将继续
reaction of the request so basically we
请求的反应，所以基本上我们
would have to send the result the
将不得不发送结果
response back to the client we can also
回复客户，我们也可以
cancel the request we can also configure
取消请求我们也可以配置
the request to set some timeout and so
请求设置一些超时等等
the thing that is key and that is really
关键是关键
important to keep in mind is that the
请记住，重要的是
underlying thread is still blocking and
基础线程仍在阻塞，并且
it will be blocked until the resistance
它将被阻止直到阻力
is being sent to the client and the
被发送到客户端，并且
client will block until it has the
客户端将阻止，直到它具有
response so that is a key aspect
反应，这是一个关键方面
to keep in mind so if we try to look at
要记住，所以如果我们尝试看看
a basic schema that would be big that
一个基本的架构会很大
would work we have a child that would
会工作，我们有一个孩子，
issue a Request on the south side we
在南侧发出请求
have our Czech Terez
有我们的捷克特雷斯
container that would process the request
可以处理请求的容器
and then on both sides of the connection
然后在连接的两侧
the IO the treads are blocked so that
IO踏板被阻塞，因此
means that on the server side the ioad
表示在服务器端的ioad
thread which is in orange on my Clyde is
我的克莱德橘黄色的线是
locked
已锁定
so my Jack's rest application is running
所以我杰克的rest应用程序正在运行
at some point in time one of the
在某个时间点之一
dejected methods will basically suspend
沮丧的方法基本上会暂停
the request by injecting the suspended
通过注入暂停请求
I think response object we now have the
我认为我们现在有了回应对象
ability to do the processing so the
进行处理的能力
business logic to get those the response
获得那些响应的业务逻辑
in a different thread so typically we're
在不同的线程中，所以通常
in Java environment we do that using a
在Java环境中，我们使用
managed fixture services and then
托管灯具服务，然后
extract that's an example once we have
摘录就是一个例子
the results available from that external
可从外部获得的结果
thread we would use the result the sorry
线程，我们将使用结果抱歉
the resume to basically send that to the
简历，基本上将其发送给
clamp until then the client is locked
直到客户端被锁定为止
and the i/o thread on server hours about
和服务器小时的I / O线程大约
so we invoke the I think response resume
所以我们调用了我认为响应简历
later to basically resume the execution
以后基本上恢复执行
of the response and the Jersey container
响应和Jersey容器
is now able to send the response back to
现在可以将响应发送回
the client and until then the child is
客户，直到那个孩子
blocked
受阻
now that the client has the response is
现在客户有了响应
ready isn't blocked anymore so it can
准备就绪不再受阻，因此可以
continue to work do something that we
继续工作做一些我们
are typically used on the server side
通常在服务器端使用
one we have long-running rest operation
一种我们长期运行的休息手术
so it works like this so we do a post
所以它像这样工作，所以我们做一个帖子
request some long-running operation
请求一些长时间运行的操作
happen and then at some point in time we
发生，然后在某个时间点，我们
send a response back to the client so we
发送回复给客户，所以我们
would send something like a 201 through
将通过发送201
the resources being created and there's
正在创建的资源，
the location of the resources now we
资源的位置现在我们
might want to use a different patterns
可能想要使用其他模式
to solve
解决
test use case so same approach we first
测试用例，所以我们首先使用相同的方法
the current will post request and then
当前将发布请求，然后
the server would answer directly with a
服务器将直接回答
202 which is basically mean I've
202这基本上意味着我已经
accepted the redzone the resource
接受redzone资源
creation but I know it will take time so
创作，但我知道这需要时间
what this ever will do it will tell the
这将做什么会告诉
client ok I will now work on creating
客户端好，我现在将致力于创建
that resources but I know that it will
这些资源，但我知道它将
take time so please come back later to
需要时间，请稍后再返回
see what when this is done the server
看看服务器什么时候完成
would also send send some temporary
还会发送一些临时
location that the client can use to get
客户可以用来获取的位置
by the key or the status of that
通过键或状态
resource creation so that mean that the
资源创建，这意味着
can't charity to issue requests against
不能慈善地针对
that temp temporary or resource using
该临时或资源使用
the complication that was send back to
被发送回的并发症
him and then the server would answer
他，然后服务器将回答
something like 200 so that means ok so
大概是200左右
this is a valid temporary resource and
这是有效的临时资源，
disabled has also the ability to add
残疾人也有能力增加
additional details like for example I'm
其他详细信息，例如我
expecting that resources together
一起期待资源
available in the next 20 seconds so it
在接下来的20秒内可用
would basically give an indication on to
基本上会给
the client when they can expect the
客户何时可以期望
resources to give it available so and
资源使其可用
then the can that's only time will do a
那只有时间的罐子会做一个
request against the same temporary
针对同一临时工的要求
location and if it has been created the
位置以及是否已创建
server so the rest server endpoint would
服务器，以便其余服务器端点
issue a 3 and 3 all trick which is a
发出3和3的所有把戏
c-collar so it buddy came in that the
C领所以哥们进来了
request has been created and it's a
请求已创建，这是一个
basically ever redirect to the new array
基本上曾经重定向到新数组
of the resources which has been created
已创建的资源
after a post so that response would
在帖子之后，以便回复
include not only the 303 which is a
不仅包括303
redirect but also the location of the
重定向，但也的位置
the final location of the resources
资源的最终位置
which had been created in the first
在第一个中创建的
place so this is something that we would
的地方，所以这是我们要
use one we have a long-running operation
使用一个我们长期运行的操作
this is a popular patterns for showing
这是显示的流行模式
that case so it basically avoid to the
这样的话，基本上可以避免
client to have to wait
客户必须等待
in the case where resources takes a lot
在很多资源的情况下
of time to be graded on the server
在服务器上分级的时间
now let's talk about something that
现在让我们谈论一些
might be useful in that specific use
在特定用途中可能会有用
case and a tea service and event so ICC
案例，茶水服务和活动，因此ICC
is a widely used mechanism that is
是一种广泛使用的机制
basically used to send payload from the
主要用于从
server side to connected client this is
服务器端到连接的客户端，这是
something which is widely used on the
被广泛使用的东西
web there is a well-defined standard for
网络上有一个明确定义的标准
that it's one way only
那只是一种方式
so that means that the can't establish
所以这意味着不能建立
the connection once the connection is
一旦连接是
established the server has the led to
建立服务器已导致
push from the server some payload to
从服务器推送一些负载到
that connected client so the client has
该连接的客户端，以便客户端具有
no way to push notification from the
无法从
client to the server this is really one
客户端到服务器，这真的是一个
way only
仅方式
but we could typically use that
但我们通常可以使用
mechanism to allow the server to send
允许服务器发送的机制
some notification to the plant for
通知工厂
example when a long-running operation is
长时间运行的操作的示例
done so as I see something that has been
这样做是因为我看到了
added to eject or s21
添加到弹出或s21
so the jax-ur is to one they really
所以jax-ur是他们真正的
introduce different new object like a
引入不同的新对象，例如
sassy event so when this event is body
骚动事件，因此当此事件为身体时
clip of a presentation of in service and
在职演示文稿的剪辑和
event it's a super interface that is
如果它是一个超级接口
extended by two interface on one hand we
一方面通过两个接口扩展
have outbound ACC event which is the
有出站ACC事件是
self side representation of an SS event
SS事件的自我表示
and on the other hand we have inbound
另一方面，我们有入站
SEC event which is a client side view of
SEC事件是客户端的视图
a server sent event so on the server
服务器发送事件，因此在服务器上
side we have the led to create event on
方面，我们带领创建活动
the client side we don't have the
客户端，我们没有
ability to create event again this is
再次创建事件的能力是
one way only so on the client side we
只有这样，在客户端，我们
are just consuming server sent events
只是消耗服务器发送的事件
that have been pushed by the server if
服务器已推送的
we look at the API while we have this
我们在查看API的同时
new SSE even think object which is
新上交所甚至认为对象是
basically a connection between a server
基本上是服务器之间的连接
and a client
和一个客户
restaurant point and that is used to
餐厅点，用来
string SS event so this is basically the
字符串SS事件，所以这基本上是
server side view of an SSE connection to
与SSE连接的服务器侧视图
API allows us to group
API使我们可以分组
multiple connections or multiple asset
多个连接或多个资产
even thing in one object which is a
甚至一个物体中的东西
broadcaster and SEC broadcaster and the
广播公司和SEC广播公司以及
idea is that Elizabeth chapter is just a
想法是伊丽莎白章只是
collection of connected kind so if you
连接种类的集合，所以如果你
are pushing a payload to an ACC
正在将有效载荷推入ACC
broadcaster it will be able to magically
广播公司将能够神奇地
push to all the connected client if you
如果您推送到所有连接的客户端
look at the our wit works using the CC
看看我们使用CC的智慧作品
API you well we see that it's very
API，您好，我们看到它非常
simple so we have this method we inject
很简单，所以我们注入了这种方法
to object the first one so this is a
反对第一个，所以这是一个
server-side you so on the server we are
服务器端您在服务器上
injecting the SS even thing which is the
注入SS甚至是
connection between the server and the
服务器与服务器之间的连接
trend and we are also injecting the SSE
趋势，我们也在注入上证所
object which is a convenient object that
方便的对象
we can use for example to create easily
我们可以使用例如轻松创建
SS event then all it takes is to
SS事件，那么所有要做的就是
basically leverage the existing jax-rs
基本上利用现有的jax-rs
annotation so we're using the pad get
注解，所以我们使用pad get
annotation in this particular case our
在这种特殊情况下，我们的注释
sse endpoint will be exposed using the
sse端点将使用
SSE endpoint and it produced that
SSE端点，它产生了
specific media type service and event
特定媒体类型的服务和事件
media type then our method do something
媒体类型，然后我们的方法做点什么
and obviously at component time we are
显然在分班时
expecting to push some payload to the
期望将一些有效载荷推向
trend for example to tell the time that
例如趋势告诉时间
- a very runny
-非常流鼻涕
- long-running operation is done so now
-现在可以进行长时间运行的操作
the current can fetch the actual
当前可以获取实际
indifferent give resources and to do
冷漠地给予资源和去做
that we just need to invoke the send
我们只需要调用发送
method on the connection object so in
连接对象上的方法
this case even King dots an and
在这种情况下，即使国王点一个和
obviously we have to send some actual
显然，我们必须发送一些实际的
payload so for that we are creating an
有效负载，因此我们正在创建一个
event and we can use the SSC object to
事件，我们可以使用SSC对象
have that gives us a shortcut and energy
有给我们捷径和精力
way to create some SS event we can do
创建一些我们可以做的SS事件的方法
that multiple times as needed by the
根据需要多次
business logic of our application so
我们应用程序的业务逻辑
here the ID would be to send
这里的ID是要发送的
notification to the connected client to
通知连接的客户端
specify that that specific on running
指定特定于运行
operation is done
操作完成
and if the tea at some point in time we
如果在某个时间点喝茶，我们
would have to close that SEC connection
将不得不关闭该SEC连接
object now if we look at the client side
如果我们看看客户端，现在反对
we also have an object that's working on
我们还有一个正在处理的对象
the connection but now from the client
连接，但现在来自客户端
to the server so it's called as a
到服务器，因此称为
seventh source to consume is this event
消耗的第七个来源是此事件
on the client side we are using the JAXA
在客户端，我们正在使用JAXA
rise to one channel side API we need to
上升到一个通道侧API，我们需要
first create a connection so as each
首先创建一个连接
event source we set the word free source
事件源，我们将单词free source设置为
target of ours at the endpoint we have
我们在终点的目标
the ability to configure that connection
配置该连接的能力
so in this example we set the
因此，在此示例中，我们将
reconnecting interval to five second and
重新连接间隔为五秒，然后
so on and we see we need to make sure
等等，我们看到我们需要确保
that we actually involve
我们实际上涉及
invoke the build method to actually
调用build方法来实际
convert that object so we now have our
转换那个对象，所以我们现在有了
connection what we have to do next is to
连接我们接下来要做的是
register some callback the first
首先注册一些回调
callback that I'm registering in this
我正在此注册的回调
example is a in Bangladesh even consumer
例如在孟加拉国甚至一个消费者
so it's basically a consumer that we
所以我们基本上是消费者
consume incoming event in this example
在此示例中使用传入事件
the only thing that my consumer is doing
我的消费者所做的唯一一件事
is just print what as beans and I have
只是打印像豆一样的东西，我有
the ability to register different
注册不同的能力
consumer for example I can register a
消费者，例如我可以注册一个
travel consumer that will be invoking
将要调用的旅行消费者
something goes wrong and finally what I
出问题了，最后我
need to do is to invoke the open method
需要做的是调用open方法
on the SS events or so on the connection
在SS事件等方面
itself so that's basically where I tell
本身，这基本上就是我告诉的地方
my container that I want my client side
我想要我的客户端的容器
container to establish the connection to
建立与之连接的容器
my remote decision point and the
我的远程决策点和
container the client-side container will
客户端容器将容器
do all the heavy lifting for me so it
为我做所有繁重的工作
will establish the connection it will
将建立连接，它将
register also callbacks and so on and as
还注册回调等等
soon as my connection is established and
建立连接后，
any time some payload is being sent from
任何时候从发送一些有效载荷
the server to the client my inbound
服务器到客户端我的入站
decision even consumer will be
决定甚至消费者
automatically invoked for me and if you
自动为我调用，如果您
see once I'm done I need to make sure
看到一旦我完成，我需要确保
that I actually close my client ID
我实际上关闭了我的客户ID
connection so the ID is just either
连接，因此ID要么是
Jack's arrest one having a status report
杰克逮捕了一名状态报告人
and it might be useful to use
这可能会有用
I said she support when we have on the
我说她支持我们
south side longer in operation let's
南侧运行时间更长
rocket
火箭
so uh today we have discussed jax-rs
所以今天我们讨论了jax-rs
basically we have talked about Jax
基本上我们已经谈论过Jax
mainly about Jax raised to the zero
主要关于Jax升至零
which is the current version of this
这是当前版本
specification it's part of device seven
规范，它是设备七的一部分
but we can also be used just on top of
但我们也可以仅用于
jealousy and we have also discussed some
嫉妒，我们也讨论了一些
of those x-rays to one new capability
这些X射线的一种新功能
that are part of Java yet where again
那是Java的一部分
they can be used in just Java C so the
它们可以在Java C中使用，所以
two capability the two new capability
两种能力两种新能力
that we have discussed are the new a
我们已经讨论过的是新的
synchronous for active account API or
同步活动帐户API或
Jax rs21 and also the introduction of
Jax rs21以及
this report so jax-rs is a standard base
该报告，因此jax-rs是标准基础
restful framework and it has support for
宁静的框架，它支持
the service sites in the beginning and
最初的服务站点和
singe access to we have added support
单访问我们已添加了支持
for client-side API that is standard
适用于标准的客户端API
base is the fact that you can basically
事实是您基本上可以
choose which implementation are you are
选择您是哪种实现
using today I've used a Jersey but I
今天使用了球衣，但我
mean you take that code and logically it
表示您采用该代码，并且在逻辑上
would work on any standard checkers
适用于任何标准检查器
implementation on the client side we
在客户端实施
have discussed the client side container
已经讨论了客户端容器
that basically do all the heavy lifting
基本上完成了所有繁重的工作
for us so it provides a very high-level
对我们来说，它提供了一个非常高级的
and simple to use API to consume rest
简单易用的API消耗休息时间
endpoints it has three invoker injector
端点具有三个调用程序注入器
eyes - so injectors 2.0 we have a
眼睛-喷油器2.0我们有一个
synchronous capability which is the
同步能力是
default in default invoker we also have
在默认调用者中，我们也有默认
an a synchronous invoker and injector
同步调用者和注入器
act one we are having a tub a
行动一个，我们有一个浴缸
synchronous reactive invoker and
同步反应调用程序和
typically you would use that reactive
通常您会使用该反应式
invoker when you have multiple services
当您有多个服务时调用
that need to be invoked and wonder
需要被调用并想知道
dependency between those remote services
这些远程服务之间的依赖性
in terms of performance I think that
在性能方面，我认为
it's fair to say that the pure a
可以说，纯净的
synchronous invoker reverse is as fast
同步调用方反向速度一样快
as the synchronous reactive invoker
作为同步反应调用者
so it's only really when you have
所以只有当你有
dependency between services that
服务之间的依赖关系
you really need to look at the new
你真的需要看看新的
invoker that will be part of Jax rise to
将成为Jax一部分的调用者
one
一
the reactive invoker using the Java ec8
使用Java ec8的反应式调用程序
completion state API this is a mandatory
完成状态API，这是强制性的
per third check first one specification
每三项检查第一个规格
but it said that we also recognize that
但它说我们也认识到
there are already actual solutions out
已经有实际的解决方案
there so the specification is open to
那里的规范是开放的
tough party rectified works so for
顽强的党整改工程，因此
example Georgi support to the arocs Java
示例Georgi对arocs Java的支持
I will travel to and reasonable features
我会去和合理的功能
from guava and the only thing that is
来自番石榴，唯一的是
mandated is the support for the
授权是对
compression stage api and it will up to
压缩阶段api，它将达到
the implementation to decide which
实施决定哪一个
additional frameworks they are going to
他们将要使用的其他框架
support we've talked about jack first on
首先我们讨论过杰克的支持
the server side so we saw this java this
服务器端，所以我们看到了这个Java
capability and this has increased ins
能力，这增加了ins
capability that has united injectors to
联合喷油器的能力
that basically allows to resume the
基本上可以恢复
location of a request processing from a
来自一个请求处理的位置
different tribe we also discuss a parent
不同的部落，我们也讨论父母
that is used for long-running operation
用于长时间运行
to avoid that the client is blocking for
避免客户端阻塞
a long time and finally we have
很长一段时间，终于我们有了
discussed our service an event which are
讨论了我们的服务事件
part of Jack's rest one might be useful
杰克休息的一部分可能会有用
when using that patterns
使用该模式时
the focus of the presentation was
演讲的重点是
rejects arrest - and also we have
拒绝逮捕-我们还有
discussed some of the technology objects
讨论了一些技术对象
rise to 1 which are part of Java 8 but
升至Java 8的1，但
Java 8 actually broader than that
Java 8实际上比这更广泛
for example moon jelly yet we have the
例如月亮果冻，但我们有
salad for API which had support for HTTP
支持HTTP的API的色拉
2 we have a new binding API to do
2我们有一个新的绑定API
mashing and amassing of Java object to
Java对象的混搭和聚集
and from JSON document we are CDI 2
从JSON文档中我们是CDI 2
which had a synchronous even capability
具有同步偶数功能
which is something that might be very
这可能是非常
nice used with objects rise to Eric's
很好地用于对象上升到埃里克的
API even that the sync capability of CDI
API甚至具有CDI的同步功能
to support also compression stage API on
也支持压缩阶段API
July 8 and so on and so on so there are
7月8日，依此类推，等等
really a lot of new stuff in July 8th
7月8日确实有很多新东西
July 8 is about modernization of the
7月8日是关于
platform and simplification of the
平台和简化
platform this is really work in progress
平台，这确实正在进行中
the goal is to finalize Java 8 this
目标是最终确定Java 8
summer we have the open source
夏天我们有开源
implementation of Java yet which is
Java的实现，这是
GlassFish 5 that will be finalized
GlassFish 5即将完成
shortly after that but in the meantime
在那之后不久，但与此同时
you can already have access to the
您已经可以访问
different Java 8 reference
不同的Java 8参考
implementation like GlassFish but also
像GlassFish这样的实现，但也
Jersey and others so I think that today
泽西岛和其他地区，所以我认为今天
you can already play with the API that
您已经可以使用该API
will be part of Java 8 including jax-rs
将成为Java 8的一部分，包括jax-rs
2.1 and in fact we have recently moved
2.1，实际上我们最近已经搬迁了
all the Java development and the last
所有Java开发以及最后
few development from java.net to get
从java.net获得的少量开发
that so so just go on github.com sorry
所以就去github.com抱歉
and you will have the ability to look at
您将可以查看
the different specification which are
不同的规格是
some are already finalized and some are
有些已经完成，有些已经
in a draft form and so you can already
以草稿形式，因此您已经可以
have access to that and are excited to
可以访问并且很高兴
do reference implementation and the ID
引用实现和ID
that we would like to get your feedback
我们希望得到您的反馈
on that before its final in the summer
在夏季决赛之前
so I
所以我
conclude with some resources that you
用一些资源总结一下
might want to check to learn more to
可能想检查以了解更多信息
learn more about this
进一步了解
the first one is check Sura
第一个是检查苏拉
specification I also encourage you to
规范，我也鼓励您
check the different an example but our
检查不同的例子，但我们
part that are in the github repo of the
在github仓库中的部分
jax-rs Whipple repository you might want
您可能想要的jax-rs Whipple存储库
to check the Jersey documentation which
检查球衣文件
has a lot of details about the
有很多关于
synchronous capability objects arrays
同步功能对象数组
so we now conclude with a question and
所以我们现在以一个问题结束
answer so feel free to raise your
回答，所以请随时提出
question and we will answer them thanks
问题，我们将回答他们，谢谢
you
您